question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                      "question": "The Sun is considered a star.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "All planets in the Solar System orbit the Sun.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                       "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The Earth revolves around the Sun in one year.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                       "question": "A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                      "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The shape of the Earth is a perfect sphere.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
